RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
- 2010, 2013-023
  - 2010
    - Unfinished Business - Senate Calendar, B-5427 to HB-5534 (Box 29)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, Resolutions to SB-256 (Box 30)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-258 to SB-489 (Box 31)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, SB-492 to HB-5256 (Box 32)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5047 to HB-5256 (Box 33)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5258 to HB-5394 (Box 34)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5400 to HB-5464 (Box 35)
    - Unfinished Business - House Calendar, HB-5465 to HB-5537 (Box 36)